Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
(Returning Pearl)
(Episode 29)
(One, write a note)
(to accompany him forever in my place.)
(Two, watch the sunrise and sunset once)
(and remember him at his best in my memories.)
(Three, make a feast)
(so he will remember the meal forever.)
(Four, eat tanghulu together.)
(Five, stay with each other for a whole day doing nothing.)
(Six, get married.)
There are still so many things
that I want to do with him
but there are only three days.
It's impossible.
Sui Sui.
The situation along the Burmese border is growing tense.
Fifth Prince and Er Kang
have volunteered
to lead the army to quell the unrest.
They will leave in two days.
Are you going as well?
His Majesty wants me to stay in the palace.
Why are you crying?
Everyone is going their separate ways.
Beautiful moments are always temporary.
Did you write all these?
Let me see.
These are
things I want to do with you.
But it's too late.
Tell me,
Sui Sui.
Which of these
do you want to do most?
I want to do all of them.
What about you?
Which one do you want to do most?
I want to do everything in the world
with you.
However, the thing I want to do most
is this.
(Get married)
Are you sure?
Getting married
is something you do with the one you spend your life with.
I'm satisfied
to see you write this down as your wish.
- Yong Qi, I want to go with you. - Don't worry. I'll be back soon.
I can fight as well.
Absolutely not.
If I bring you along,
I'll be too busy worrying about you.
How do I fight on the battlefield?
I want to go.
Listen to me.
After leaving, I'm sure you'll be gone for a while.
Xiao Yan Zi.
Lin Er.
In the story you read,
Fifth Prince and Er Kang have returned safely, right?
Zi Wei,
I guarantee
to protect myself well.
Yong Qi and I
will come back safely.
Yes.
With me in the palace,
both of you can rest assured.
I will protect the safety of both princesses
and wait for both of you to come back.
All right.
I, the Jade Pond Deity, have made a divination.
Yong Qi and Er Kang
are good men who protect the kingdom.
They will be together with Xiao Yan Zi
and Zi Wei
until they grow old.
Thank you, Jade Pond Deity.
Although we will no longer meet after we say our goodbyes today,
I, Er Kang, will forever remember your grace.
Yes. We will always miss you in this world.
Lin Er.
Shufang Hall is supposed to be bustling
but Zi Wei and I will soon be the only ones left.
Didn't you say the story you read
was a story about me?
But what I want
is for all of us to be together
without anyone leaving.
Xiao Yan Zi.
Because your story is still going on.
You are going to experience everything in life
to become the real female lead.
I don't want to become the female lead.
I only want to be Xiao Yan Zi
who eats and has fun as I wish.
Xiao Yan Zi,
it's time to grow up.
Learn well from Master Ji.
You are smart
and you have Zi Wei to accompany you.
When I return in triumph,
I hope to see a different Princess Huan Zhu.
All right.
Yong Qi, don't worry.
When you return,
I will show you a different Xiao Yan Zi.
Is this the "Painting of the Divine Dragon's Return"?
This is so majestic.
Zi Wei, this is a good method.
You will paint a dragon scale every day.
If you do that, the divine dragon will manifest itself
after 81 days
and they will return.
Not just me. We will paint it together.
I'm using the "Ninety-nine Days of Winter Solstice Diagram" as a reference.
By doing this, when we miss them,
we can count how many unpainted dragon scales are left
to see how many days are left until their triumphant return.
Yes.
Come on.
No, Zi Wei.
I'm worried that my drawing skills are bad.
If the divine dragon gets angry,
it won't manifest itself.
You should do it.
Xiao Yan Zi, being sincere is the most important thing.
Whether you do good or not isn't important.
Hold it.
After I leave,
Jing Yuan will probably miss me like this.
After all, he doesn't belong to this world.
I forcefully added him in.
However,
having a group of like-minded friends,
he will probably be happy
even without me.
(He is born from love. Without love, he'll be gone.)
(Jing Yuan was forcefully added by you.)
(After you leave, he will vanish.)
Vanish?
How?
How will he vanish?
What do you mean?
(It's all an illusion, there's no need to be obsessed.)
- Lin Er. - Lin Er.
What's wrong, Lin Er?
I can't do it.
I...
I'm going to find Jing Yuan.
Lin Er.
- Lin Er. - Lin Er!
Jing Yuan.
Sui Sui.
Jing Yuan, I'm not leaving.
- I'm not leaving. - Sui Sui, calm down.
What happened?
I'm not leaving.
I'm not going to leave.
Speak slowly.
It's all right.
What happened?
If I leave...
If I leave, you'll vanish.
What?
The System said
you were a character I forcefully added.
Once I leave,
you will vanish.
I see.
Sui Sui.
Actually,
this is also a good thing.
Since I was born because of you,
it is only natural
for me to vanish
after you return.
Jing Yuan, I don't want that.
Instead of living like a zombie
after you leave,
it's better to let me vanish into thin air.
Perhaps I can go to your world
and accompany you by your side.
I don't want that.
Jing Yuan,
I'd rather not go back
than see you vanish.
Sui Sui,
I'd rather vanish
than see you stay here.
Listen to me.
We'll let everything
return to its original state.